

DETAILS

Phone

778 - 814 - 7556

Email

d.mcleod088@gmail.com

Location

#26 10738 133 Street,

Surrey, BC

Portfolio

<u>https://donnaamm. github.io/portfolio/</u>

SKILLS

Photoshop Illustrator InDesign After Effects HTML/CSS Photography

PROFILE

Determined and motivated to provide high quality service and work. Efficient at ensuring all tasks and deadlines are completed in a timely manner. Continuous learner able to quickly adapt to changing work environments and technology. I am a problem solver with excellent time management aiming to find a suitable position to further develop my skills and experience and to help a company succeed.

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATES

Graphic Design Technology Diploma September 2021-July 2022 Vancouver Career College, Surrey

Hairdressing, DiplomaSeptember 2012-Auguest 2013
Hair Art Academy, Surrey

Responsive Web Design CertificateFreecampcode, Online

Graphic Design Tips & Tricks CertificateJuly 2022

Linkedin Learning, Online

EXPERIENCE

Reception/Optometric AssistantCotober 2015-March 2021
Langley Eyecare Centre, Langley

Hairstylist September 2014-February 2015 Champers Hair And Spa, Surrey

Hairstylist September 2013-April 2014 *Prism Hair Designs, Langley*

Cashier March 2012-December 2012 Green Timbers Liquor Store, Surrey

Financial Customer Service Representative April 2009-April 2012 Cash Store Financial, Surrey/Langley